Brent Hackman

Web Developer

440 A W 28th Division Hwy, Lititz, PA 17543

P: 717.283.8345

E: brenthack35@gmail.com

Profile:

A Web Developer with over 17 years of overall experience in design and development of web-based applications, e-commerce solutions, websites and responsive/mobile. Brent has proven his success in his field by providing high-end work to clients such as Vanscoy Maurer & Bash, M&P Amusement, Pyramid Healthcare, Drug Plastics, Xhema Industries, Blackbaud, ING, Western Union, Spotzer Media, K-12 Schools, Ronald McDonald House, Easter Seals, Accion World-Wide and many others. He has extensive knowledge of developing for Applications, Web and Mobile. He exemplifies great communication skills and has a very strong work ethic. He has a passion for learning and taking on new challenges.

Professional Experience:

Web Talent Marketing

Dates: March 2019 - October 2019

Title: Web Developer

Responsibilities: Front-End Web Development with Wordpress, Shopify, HTML, CSS, SaSS, Javascript, database building, PHP, Responsive/mobile Design. Worked closely with project management team, designers and clients to produce high-end cutting-edge websites.

JandBhack Designs Dates: 2016 - Current

Title: Owner/Web Developer/Designer

Responsibilities: Consulting, marketing, SEO, design, creative services, web design, web

development, application development, mobile development/design, responsive,

prototyping, logo development, brand creation, photography

Dates: AUG 2011 - September 2016

Employer: Blackbaud, Inc.

Title: Senior Interactive Designer III

Responsibilities included design and development using Blackbaud's Suite of CRM/CMS solutions including NetCommunity, Altru, Luminate Online, TeamRaiser, Raisers Edge, Constituent Management. Design and Develop multiple online applications, websites, mobile solutions, donation form customizations, including Sphere's *Friends Asking Friends* online based donation sites and fundraising tools. Maintain and build SQL Databases for an array of custom Wordpress solutions and clients. Very involved at the project level with strong communication, project management and client engagements.

Dates: OCT 2007 - AUG 2011 **Employer:** Perficient, Inc.

Title: Senior Interactive Developer/Technical Consultant

Work included HTML & CSS, Flash, Action Scripting, jQuery, Javascript, Mobile Design and

Web Design for multiple clients worldwide.

Dates: APRIL 2002 - MAY 2007

Employer: ING

Title: Senior Graphic/Web Designer

Worked for in-house creative team. His work included interactive Flash presentations,

electronic email campaigns, print collateral and marketing materials.

Dates: MAY 2001 - NOV 2002 Employer: The Ball Group

Title: Web Designer

Worked for in-house Ad Agency. His work included Print collateral, Web Design and

Development.

Portfolio Examples:

2019 - M&P Amusement https://mpamusement.com/

Custom Responsive Shopify e-Commerce Build & Re-Design

2019 - Vanscoy Maurer & Bash Jewelers

https://vmbjewelers.com/

Custom Responsive Shopify e-Commerce Build & Design

2019 - Shyft Careers

https://www.shyftcareers.com/

Custom Responsive Wordpress Build & Design

2019 - Pyramid Healthcare

https://www.pyramidhealthcarepa.com/

Custom Wordpress Build

2018 - Xhema Industires

http://xhema.com

Custom Responsive Jekyll Static Site Portfolio - Design and Build

2016 - Wyoming Stock Growers Land Trust

http://www.wsgalt.org/

Custom Responsive WordPress Design and Build

2016 - Tennyson Center for Children

http://www.tennysoncenter.org/

Custom Responsive WordPress Design and Build

2015 - Dentech USA

http://dentech-usa.com/

Custom Responsive WordPress Design and Build

2013 - Accion World-Wide

http://www.accion.org

Blackbaud NetCommunity (BBNC-CMS), HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript

Skills:

WordPress, Shopify, Jekyll, Markdown, Liquid Syntax, HUGO, Node.js, Vue.js, HTML5, CSS, SASS, CSS Flex, CSS Grid, Bootstrap, RSS, jQuery, Javascript, JSON, Sharepoint, Ruby, PHP, MySQL, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Google Maps API's, Adobe Creative Suite, Sketch, Microsoft Office Suite, Visual Studio, git, GitHub, MAMP, Cornerstone SVN and anything else I can get my hands on.

Education & Certificates:

1999-2001 - Associates Degree in Multimedia Design & Specialized Technology from Bradley Academy for the Visual Arts, York, PA (Art Institute of York)

Awards & Publications:

2010 - Who's Who in Perficient, Inc. - Featured Article in Perficient's Printed Newsletter 2001 - Who's Who in Design Award - Bradley Academy For the Visual Arts

Interests:

Live Music, Hiking, Traveling, Golf, Kayaking, Fishing, Art, History